const STORE = [ 

    { 
      number: 1,
      question: "Who is leading the NBA in 3pt fg?",
      answers: ["Steph Curry", "James Harden", "Klay Thompson", "Damian Lilard"], 
      correctAnswer: "James Harden"
    },
  
    {
      number: 2,
      question: "Who won the NBA Coach of the Year award in 2019?",
      answers: ["Nate McMillan", "Michael Malone", "Michael Budenholzer", "Doc Rivers"],
      correctAnswer: "Michael Budenholzer"
    },
  
    {  
      number: 3,
      question: "Who was the 2017-2018 NBA MVP?",
      answers: ["Steph Curry", "Lebron James", "James Harden", "Russell Westbrook"],
      correctAnswer: "James Harden"
    },
  
    { 
      number: 4, 
      question: "Who is the all time leader in 3pt field goals?", 
      answers: ["Reggie Miller", "Steph Curry", "James Harden", "Ray Allen"],
      correctAnswer: "Ray Allen"
    },
  
    { 
      number: 5, 
      question: "Who is the NBA GOAT?",
      answers: ["Kobe Bryant", "Lebron James", "Michael Jordan", "Shaquille Oneal"],
      correctAnswer: "Kobe Bryant"
    },
  
    { 
      number: 6,
      question: "Who is the first person in NBA history to average a triple double?", 
      answers: ["Oscar Roberson", "Lebron James", "Russell Westbrook", "Grant Hill"],
      correctAnswer: "Oscar Roberson"
    },
  
    {
      number: 7,
      question: "Who is the first person to average a triple double in 3 consecutive seasons?", 
      answers: ["Oscar Roberson", "Lebron James", "Russell Westbrook", "Grant Hill"],
      correctAnswer: "Russell Westbrook"
    },
  
    {
      number: 8,
      question: "Who holds the record for most 3pt fg in a season?", 
      answers: ["Reggie Miller", "Kyle Korver", "Steph Curry", "Klay Thompson"],
      correctAnswer: "Steph Curry"
    },
      
    { 
      number: 9,
      question: "Who holds the record for most 3pt fg in a game?",
      answers: ["Reggie Miller", "Kyle Korver", "Steph Curry", "Klay Thompson"],
      correctAnswer: "Klay Thompson"
    },
    
    {  
      number: 10,
      question: "Who holds the all time record for most assist?",
      answers: ["Chris Paul", "Mark Jackson", "Gary Payton", "John Stockton"],
      correctAnswer: "John Stockton"
    }
  ]